[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Do we know how old the young victims were, outside of the math teacher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "And is there any clues, Stephanie, stage about motive or who the intended target was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "They don't know just yet and if they do, they haven't told us.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stephanie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Without naming the boy who we believe did this, because we cannot do that at the stage, did you know him personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Yeah, I knew the person with the gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Why do you think he would possibly do this with a gun and shoot such a well liked teacher and indeed, some of his school colleagues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "I believe it was because I saw him getting bullied a couple of times and I think he took out his bullying on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Obviously, as every parents' nightmares, Tabatha that your kid goes to school and gets caught up in a shooting like this and what is your take on what happened today and what do you know about the family and this boy who might have committed the shooting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Well, I know that he knows my daughter personally and she always said just wonderful things about him and that he was, you know, getting picked on pretty regular and that, you know, but he always had the smile, he was always, you know, just a very nice boy to everybody and so it's just, you know, I just find it difficult to get that he, you know, he got bullied but he didn't have anybody to talk to, that he didn't have anybody to go to in the school before he decided to do this, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "PERSON": ["Tabatha"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Do you believe that teachers, that some people say, should be armed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "No, I mean, it's just sad that this happened at all guns at school, you know, junior high, just, you know, bullying, all of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "They're going to be OK, but do you know them, and what do you think about what happened to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I did not know them but I did know that they were friends of the shooter and I believe that -- I'm just happy they're OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "What is your reaction to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Well it's pretty sad, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "What do you think Mr. Mayor is the answer to this unrelenting tidal wave of gun violence in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mayor"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"]}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Do you know much about him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "You know, I don't know much about Mike.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["earlier today"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Rose Garden"]}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "As suppose you have this question I would ask you about all this is what guarantees were given to the President that ObamaCare and its system were ready to go live and who gave them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, there's a lot of fascination obviously with pointing the finger of blame for the fact that the website associated with the Affordable Care Act has not been performing as effectively as it should be, and no one is more frustrated by that than the President as he said earlier today in the Rose Garden.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", ":", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "At what point if this continue, say we're in I don't know six weeks time or two months time and you're having the same about of difficulty with the system, at what point do you consider a head rolling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "It shouldn't be about, you know, making -- having heads roll or firing people, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "If it's not him who's it going to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "In terms of the other obvious question which is the penalty that comes from the end of March, you have to subscribe by then or get a penalty, have you considered delaying that and at what point would you consider delaying that if the answer is no at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, first of all, it's important to know, Piers, that we're three weeks into a six month process so this is still very early days.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["March"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["McCain"]}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "He tempted to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, I don't think Senator McCain is far off in what we're talking about here in front of the tax surge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Karmel, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "I'm doing fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "``", "UH", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 187, "question": "What was going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Mostly, \"Oh no, don't faint.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "You see yourself as a great example of ObamaCare at its finest as the president himself led back to save you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "It's a funny metaphor I suppose.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "UH", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "And what did he say to you after with the president (inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "He was, you know, he asked how I was doing, make sure I was OK and, I mean, I was extremely appreciative of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple", "Amazon.com"]}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Isn't it that true though Amy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "No, I mean think conservative and libertarians would say, if something is this deeply flawed like at Apple product or a flat screen TV or Amazon.com, you don't have to buy it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Did a civil war after which will come a more cohesive united Republican Party which actually in the end may have a better chance to win the election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "VBN", "JJ", "NNP", "WDT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "We've got to get this out of sports.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Could he not in the end win this civil war in his own policy (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "I agree with all of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "If you insist (ph) bigger disasters, it appears to be, shouldn't she be resigning (inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ":", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I don't think we have all the information.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Are you serious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "She was in-charge of this website.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Why, I though you love it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ",", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Because -- no, that's not the only prevision.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 353, "question": "At what point do we say a head must roll if it doesn't work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I mean that's just ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Who's been your favorite scoundrel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Oh, God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Which is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "I mean when you done the show 18 years, it was even incredible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Do it live?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "No, the other part that you just said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "And what's been your favorite moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Oh God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "What's the moment you relive again personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "I don't know that I relive it again but it certainly struck me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Why is it, Deborah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "... have no access.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Deborah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Why is it that nothing ever changes in America after all these gun outrages?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "I don't know that you can say that nothing ever changes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "I mean you are -- could have make -- you're in good nick for 86, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "MD", "VB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Sorry, excuse me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Does that give you any qualms at all, Edward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "It makes me feel very fortunate and I just think that, well, it's difficult for people to understand, and I know that certainly, if it's not unique, it's certainly very unusual, but we're happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Edward?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Excuse me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "She's not going to have a baby.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Why would you do that to a child?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 565, "question": "And pretty most of your technical question, which is silly, I don't mean to be impertinent, but how have you managed to have a baby at 86?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RBS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Some time ago, when I had a reverse vasectomy, the doctor without my knowledge stored some sperm and when I got out of prison I was made aware of it and ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$750,000"]}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "And what was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "$750,000.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "But actually, he hasn't got money or gold, isn't that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "No, he doesn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Do you have any guilt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "A little bit, but not a whole lot, not enough to be classified as a gold digger.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "I mean I -- as much (inaudible), I mean do you think this is for life or you think you may have more young wives as we go on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "I'm the last one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "How can you be such sure of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "It's in here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Is it as bad as you've ever known it, the poison and the ranks there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I'm a life long Democrat and hardly in the position to critique the Republican Party.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Do you change diapers, Edwin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edwin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Are you good at it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Do you recommend having an 86-year-old boy toy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Of course, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Well, if it works for you, I mean I'm happy with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "You got one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]